RONYA GETTIS

St. Louis Park, MN

Phone: 507-649-0822 | Email: klmirg6@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ronya-gettis/ | GitHub: https://github.com/klmirg

Portfolio: https://klmirg.github.io/ronya-react-portfolio/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with over 15 years of background in Customer Service. Recently earned a certificate in full stack web development from the University of Minnesota Coding Bootcamp, with newly developed skills using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js as well as responsive web design and much more. Effective at combining creativity and problem solving to develop user-friendly applications. Known among co-workers as someone who takes enormous pride in her work and pays very close attention to detail no matter the complexity of the project.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, SQL, HTML/CSS, MERN

Database: MySQL, NoSQL

Other: Bootstrap, ¡Query, Inquirer, Jest, Sequelize, Mongoose, Handlebars, Heroku, Git, JSON, API's, OOP,

MVC, PWA's

PROJECTS

BookShelf | https://github.com/klmirg/BookShelf.git | https://bookshelf22.herokuapp.com

- BookShelf was created for the book lovers out there, who would love to have a digital collection of their favorite books, as well as be able to search new titles for future reads.
- Responsibilities were to create all of the routes, the models, and the views.
- Technologies used: Node.js, Express, MySql, Handlebars, Nodemon, Bootstrap, and Google Book API

Dinder | https://github.com/klmirg/doggy-days.git | http://dinder-dog.herokuapp.com

- Dinder is a mobile application that allows you to randomly search dogs, and save your favorites, to help you narrow down your choices in your search for your new pup!
- Responsibilities of mine were to create the login/signup modal, and make sure people are actually able to sign in or sign up. As well as the option to remove a favorite dog.
- Technologies that were used: MERN, GraphQL, Apollo Client, React Bootstrap, and The Dog API

EXPERIENCE:

Server, Shift Leader

2007-2022

Basil's Pizza Northfield, MN

- Educate new employees in restaurant policies and processes to ensure consistency throughout all
 employees.
- Supervise a team of 10 or more employees consisting of cooks, delivery drivers, and servers.
- Empower employees to challenge themselves and gain new skills throughout the restaurant. Inspiring constant improvement throughout the staff.

Bartender, Supervisor

2016-2020

Burger Jones Minneapolis, MN

• Awarded an Employee recognition spotlight out of thousands of employees throughout the company.

- Captured data for multiple reports; monitoring financials with the use of Compeat Management Systems, Micros, Simphony, and Excel.
- Reduced labor costs up to 7% by adjusting staff accordingly based on labor and sales, generating increased revenue for the company.

Bartender, Server 2012-2016

Oggi's Pizza and Brewing Company

Del Mar, CA

- Influenced a customer-focused mindset to provide exceptional service and resolution. Often resulting in repeat customers.
- Established healthy relationships with customers and employees by resolving any inquiries or complaints.
- Provided quality customer service to ensure a high rate of customer retention.

Server 2012-2016

Buca Di Beppo Carlsbad, CA

- Retained customers through cultivating positive and professional relationships.
- Determined customer needs through analyzing verbal and non-verbal communication cues. Resulting in happier customers
- Maintained knowledge and compliance with state sanitation laws to ensure accuracy of cleanliness throughout the restaurant.
- Trained biannually with the state's liquor laws to maintain the safety of customers and employees while serving alcohol.

Mailroom Processor 2011-2012

Rust Consulting Faribault, MN

- Implemented knowledge of all new and old procedures of the 100's of cases to maximize accuracy.
- Ensured all documents were scanned, filed, collated, and sealed properly according to procedures for each individual case to sustain organization and precision.
- Modeled a positive working relationship with clients, agencies, and coworkers to promote a positive quality service image.

EDUCATION:

University of Minnesota Coding Bootcamp

Full Stack Web Developer Certificate, March 2022

References Upon Request